What time are you coming
over on our next day off?
Misuzu? When did you make plans to do that?
I didn't. I thought she meant you.
'Cause that's the first
time I've mentioned it.
When I throw a jab or a straight,
it always lands
But when I'm aiming for your heart,
I miss every time
Parallel, zigzagging, awkward, incoherent
When you look my way and move closer to me
I know it doesn't mean the same thing for you
But I wish we could stay like this forever
My changing feelings are driving me crazy
The moment you turn to face me,
take that! Telepathy
If only we could feel the same thing
I want to kick this pesky subtlety away
I want to know everything,
I want to know everything
I can't fool you forever
I can't keep this hidden
I want to shout out my secret, AHHH
Take that! Telepathy
Te-te-te-telepathy
Telepathy
The Girls of the Olston Family
"The Girls of the Olston Family."
Carol's House
Forest
Convenience Store
Right Here
Big Building
Building
Station
Carol really didn't put much thought
into this map she gave us.
I'm not sure if I'd even call it a map.
It should be around here,
but there's nothing but a
fence with no end in sight.
I wonder if it's some sort of facility.
It's... not here, right?
I really want to hope it isn't.
Oh! You two!
What are you doing just standing
in front of my house?
Are you bad people?
No mistaking it.
They're definitely related.
You're Carol-chan's friends?
Is that true?
Especially you, the tall one!
You don't have any perverted intentions?
Huh?!
I know that all boys are...
Oh. Breasts.
Um... For what it's worth,
I'm actually a girl.
Oh, okay! Come on in!
I want to go home.
Don't leave! I can't handle this on my own!
The path to our house is like a maze,
so make sure you follow me closely.
Even I get lost sometimes, but still...
Huh?!
I'm sure it will be just fine today!
At least, I sure hope it will be!
I'm having all of the bad feelings...
Maybe I really should go home...
Welcome back, Mummy!
I'm home, Carol-chan!
I miss you so much! I love you so much!
Oh!
Yay! Tomo-chan's here!
Hey...
Thank you for coming! You too, Misuzu-chan!
Thank—
Harsh.
Oh!
Look! We have matching braids!
Meanie.
Wh-What is this place?!
It's my room.
What are you? A princess?!
Are you a princess?!
Huh? Yeah.
No way!
Would you calm down?
She's just really rich.
This is me when I was little.
Wow...
You've always worn ribbons
in your hair, huh?
Yep. Mummy used to say
that I'm pudding.
Say what?
Pudding.
That's why I always wear soft, cute clothes.
The ribbon is the cherry,
and you can't forget the cherry!
But the most important thing is...
Not letting anyone eat you?
Huh?
How'd you know? Amazing!
I'm going to use your bathroom.
Sure. It's...
I saw it on the way in. I can find it.
Um...
Is there something you want from me?
You were mean to Carol-chan earlier.
Are you actually a bad girl?
That's what this is about?
If I said I'm friends with
her for her money...
What would you do?
I'm sorry. You're a very cute girl!
Uh, thanks...
Why do I feel like I just lost?
Tomo-chan, let's play Othello.
Sure! I won't go easy on you!
Okay, I'll be white.
5 Minutes Later
Oh, Othello?
My Misuzu here is really
good at this kind of game!
You'd better be ready!
Well, it's true that I don't often lose.
Okay, I'll be white.
10 Minutes Later
What kind of mother and daughter are you?
Huh? What do you mean?
Bye, Carol.
See you at school.
Thank you for having us.
Please come visit again sometime!
And you, too.
Come by again!
I don't know...
And last is...
Carol-chan!
Mummy!
Let's go.
Yeah.
A Feeling I Won't Give Up
"A Feeling I Won't Give Up."
Hey, Misuzu, did you hear?
We have midterms tomorrow!
I'm more shocked that
you asked me if I knew.
I completely forgot! I'm in so much trouble!
In that case, let's have
a study group today.
Really? Don't you have to study, too?
I don't mind. We can do it at my house.
Can I come, too?
Sure, I guess...
Thank you.
Stop talking like that.
Tomo!
Let's study together after school.
I'll be your tutor.
Huh?!
You'll tutor Tomo, you say?
Don't be so full of yourself.
What?
What was your ranking in our
last middle school exam?
Huh? I think I ranked around 30.
So what?
I ranked... number one.
Damn it!
I'm kinda surprised, though.
About what?
Well, you usually try to get
me and Jun together, right?
So why this ti—
I'm allowed every now
and then, too, aren't I?
Do that to me, too.
No.
I haven't been here in a while.
It looks pretty different in here now.
You haven't been here very much, either?
When we were kids, she told
me not to come to her house.
I don't remember why, though.
You don't remember?
It's because you kept breaking
everything in my house.
Oh... Th-That's right.
You just weren't the kind of child
that could play sitting down.
Even today, I'm actually super worried.
C'mon, that's not gonna
be a problem anymore!
I'm home.
Don't tell me...
Misuzu has a boyfriend?!
Mom.
Welcome home.
Hey, I'm here to visit!
Akemi?!
Uh, no, I'm her daughter...
Tomo-chan?
You do look just like her.
But don't grow up to be like her.
Uh-huh...
Nice to meet you. My name is Carol.
Most people don't get this close
when meeting for the first time.
You look just as cute as Misuzu-chan!
I'm not sold on this one.
Aw...
I'm not, either.
I don't get this at all.
It's just a long equation. It's not hard.
Let's walk through it a step at a time.
It's √10/2-√2, right?
Huh?
She's right.
For real?!
It's an easy problem, but not one you
should be able to do in your head...
I could.
Are you some kinda genius?!
How'd you do that?!
Well, these ones here are friends,
so if you whip this around here
and smoosh it onto here...
If math could be solved
that way, anyone could...
Whoa, that's amazing! It worked!
See?
Oh, man! I might be a genius!
Tomo-chan the genius!
I don't know what you did,
but in math, the process is
as important as the solution.
You won't get credit if you
can't show your work.
What a pain.
You said it! That's so inefficient!
Okay! Now I'm ready to get serious!
Me, too!
There's a lot going on here,
so you can express all this as x.
Oh, you're right! That's much better!
You're a good teacher, Misuzu-chan.
You really are. You've got a knack for this.
I'd say this much is just normal.
Don't be so modest!
I mean, you're good enough
to make me understand!
If I can keep this up,
I might actually be able to go
to the same university as you!
You want to do that?
Of course I do!
I was barely able to follow
you into this high school,
so it might not be easy,
but you're my best friend, after all!
I see...
Okay, okay. You can follow me, too.
Heck yeah!
70 • Aizawa Tomo
I'm number 70!
That's the first time I've
ever ranked in the top half!
Looks like you were in good shape this time.
Yeah! What was your rank?
I got 54!
Not bad, not great.
You're so boring.
Most people don't do stuff like this.
Well, he does.
What was your rank, Misuzu?
Second.
Wow, I should've expected as much!
Who was number one?
1 • Carol Olston
Heart-Pounding!
A Gaming Overnighter
"Heart-Pounding! A Gaming Overnighter."
I bought that game you said
you were interested in.
Winners Eleven.
Oh, nice!
My parents almost never buy me video games.
Come to think of it, when we first met,
you were a gamer kid, huh?
Hey, gamer kid!
That takes me back!
Hey, cut it out!
Never call me that again.
Wh-What's with you?
Wanna come over today?
We'll do some gaming together,
like we used to.
Really?! I can?!
Of course you can.
There's no school tomorrow,
so you can even stay over.
We can play games until super late!
A gaming overnighter, huh?
I can't wait!
I was so distracted by gaming,
I didn't realize!
I'm spending the night at Jun's house!
There's all sorts of gaming going on here.
So... can I come, too?
You'll go with me, Carol?!
This is a thing I shouldn't go to, isn't it?
If you know that, don't complicate things.
No! I shouldn't do this!
I'm gonna tell him no!
Wait, Tomo-chan.
Sit down.
Why?
Don't ask why. Just sit down.
Just sit, okay?
You telling him no...
...is not an option.
It's only at times like this
that they get along.
Tomo! Walk home with me!
Jun!
I'm, uh... walking with
Misuzu and Carol today.
Oh, okay. I'll wait for you at home, then.
S-Sure.
Fighting it is useless.
You're seeing him later anyway.
Yeah, at his house.
Going home separately actually seems
like a tease. Almost as if...
As if?
Oh, just shut up, damn it!
I'm gonna stay over at Jun's house tonight.
Huh?
Wh-What?
I see. I thought we still
had a lot more time...
But maybe it's time to start considering it.
Huh?
My grandchild's name.
You're jumping way ahead here!
Dad! I'm staying over at Jun's tonight!
Okay. Don't make too much trouble for them.
Huh?
What's the problem? You can go on over.
It's actually kinda unsettling that
they're not concerned at all.
I've been waiting for you, Tomo!
Mom told me to bring you this.
Cool, thanks! I'll let my mom know tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Yeah. She's not home today.
Went on a trip, apparently.
Why didn't you tell me that sooner?!
Huh? Did you need to talk
to my mom or something?
That's not the issue here!
You make such awesome curry, Jun.
I'll make some for you sometime.
Oh, yeah...
Every now and then... I do
want to try your cooking.
Really? Well, whenever you
want some, just ask!
Sure.
Anyway, what do you wanna
do about your bath?
Hmm... I usually take mine at night, so...
I was planning to bathe here.
Go ahead and take yours after
we're done eating, then.
I wanna keep gaming right up until bedtime.
O-Okay... I will.
I just had mine, so you can just
reheat the water and get right in.
I'll just take a shower!
Why? A good, long soak will warm you—
Just a shower!
I'll leave a towel right—
What?! Did something happen?!
N-No, nothing!
Sorry to make you wait so long.
What happened to your cheeks?
They're all red.
Huh?
Why?
The mood's so awkward for some reason.
Is Jun actually conscious of me, too?
What can I do? Should I try
saying something to him first?
Okay, Tomo!
Let's play that game!
Wait, what?!
FC VASIMR
Hill Villagers
It's been a long time.
Want me to go easy on you?
Get over yourself!
There! Go! That's it!
My pass was good! You're wide open!
Oh, yeah! And shoot!
Score!
You're not half bad.
You'll never beat me at video games, either!
Aw, damn it!
I lost again!
Because you just keep
attacking and never defend.
You need to think about how the game—
Shut up, gamer kid!
I told you not to call me that!
Okay, I'm sorry!
Wanna play another match?
Yeah, sure.
It's 9:00 already?
What do you wanna do? Stay up late?
Can you even stay up late?
Don't underestimate me!
I once stayed up until 11:30!
That's all? I've...
stayed up until midnight before.
M-Midnight?!
That's the next day!
It's not that big a deal.
Maybe...
we really can't stay up late.
Yeah, maybe.
Goodnight.
Yeah, goodnight.
It smells like Jun.
We're really just gonna go to sleep now?
It seems like such a waste.
Wait, a waste of what?!
Tomo?
You awake?
What's up?
Today was fun, huh?
Do you think we're gonna...
always be like...
Jun, I...
That jerk!
That's what his face looks like?
I'm always so close to him,
but I don't get many chances
to just look at his face.
Especially the little
details like his ears.
Oh, so this is what they look like?
What about his nose?
Oh, crap. This is kinda fun.
Wh-What is this?!
What is going on?!
Jun?!
Jun, you sleep in the weirdest positions.
Well, I'm off. See you at the dojo later.
Yeah.
In spite of everything, that was really fun.
I'm glad I came.
But I feel like I'm forgetting something...
Last night, I got to Jun's house,
ate curry,
took a shower,
played games,
went to sleep in the bed...
and woke up in the futon?!
After that, things between us...
What?
Nothing.
Okay, then.
...were like this for about a week.
(This suspicious behavior is...)
Hey, you know, I'm all mixed up
It's too complicated, I'm freaking out
I want to look cute to you
(crazy, crazy, drive me crazy, and that's…)
So I'm plotting, bargaining,
sly, and stubborn
Dizzying love
Just tell him to look at you
And watch him stiffen up even more,
because you're both so awkward
What? Even if we're alike in that way
It doesn't make me happy, 'cause it
means our love is going nowhere
Cloudy heart, swirling emotions—
I sense rain coming
So I partly open my umbrella,
then sneakily scoot closer to you
Please notice the curl of my
eyelashes as I keep blinking
And don't say I'm acting weird
All this plotting and bargaining
is my sly plan to look cute to you
Try to solve the riddle of
this soft, dizzying love
(Buzzing, fidgeting)
Listen, I might be a bit
tangled in my own web now
But once you unravel the mystery,
you'll see pure lo-love